Have you noticed how similar you are to your friends?
It may be because your brains operate in harmony with each other.
We know that friends are more likely to be the same age, gender and ethnic
background as each other.
Now it seems their brains are alike too.
We know that friends are more likely to be the same age, gender and ethnic
background as each other.
Now it seems their brains are alike too.
We know that friends are more likely to be the same age, gender and ethnic
background as each other.
Now it seems their brains are alike too.
Researchers at the University of scanned the brains of 42 classmates while they
watched videos intended to provoke varying responses.
Some researchers at University California scanned the brains of 42 classmates while
they watched videos intended to provoke varying responses.
Some researchers at of of 42 classmates while they watched videos intended to
provoke varying responses.
Some people might find a romantic scene touching, for instance, while others would
feel it was embarrassing.
The activity of friends' brains was more similar than that of people who didn't know
each other, particularly in regions involved in attention, emotion and language.
This similarity was similar to people who didn't know each other, particularly in
regions involved in attention, emotion and language.